const quizObject = [
  {
    topic: "Boxing",
    questions: [
      { id: 1, question: "Who did Carl Froch knockout at Wembley Stadium?" },
      { id: 2, question: "What city was Naseem Hamed Born In?" },
      { id: 3, question: "Micky Ward and _____ had a historic trilogy" },
      { id: 4, question: "Joe Calzaghe trained out of which Welsh town?" },
    ],
    answers: [
      {
        correct: "George Groves",
        answer: ["Mike Tyson", "George Groves", "Eddie Hearn", "Ricky Hatton"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Sheffield",
        answer: ["Sheffield", "Newport", "Barnsley", "London"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Arturo Gatti",
        answer: [
          "Arturo Gatti",
          "Floyd Mayweather",
          "Eddie Hearn",
          "Anthony Joshua",
        ],
      },
      {
        correct: "Newbridge",
        answer: ["Newbridge", "Blackwood", "Pontypool", "Port Talbot"],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "Cooking",
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question:
          "What do we call the process of submerging veggies or fruits quickly in boiling water?",
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question:
          "Which of the following kinds of pasta has its name meaning “little worms” in Italian?",
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which dish do we have when cooking beef in puff pastry?",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question:
          "Which of the following seafood is also known as the “Norwegian lobster?",
      },
    ],
    answers: [
      {
        correct: "Blanching",
        answer: ["Soaking", "Shocking", "Blanching", "Splatong"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Vermicelli",
        answer: ["Vermicelli", "Fidelini", "Spaghetti", "Frosties"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Beef Wellington",
        answer: ["Beef Wellington", "Baklava", "Shepherd`s Pie", "Cottage Pie"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Scampi",
        answer: ["Plaice", "Scallops", "Cod", "Scampi"],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "History",
    questions: [
      { id: 1, question: "What year did the battle of Hastings take place?" },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "How many wives did King Henry VIII have in his lifetime?",
      },
      { id: 3, question: "What year did World War end?" },
      { id: 4, question: "Who was the first person to land on the moon?" },
    ],
    answers: [
      {
        correct: "1066",
        answer: ["1266", "1366", "1166", "1066"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Six",
        answer: ["Five", "Six", "One", "Two"],
      },
      {
        correct: "1918",
        answer: ["1918", "1934", "1922", "1916"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Neil Armstrong",
        answer: [
          "Danny Flynn",
          "Neil Armstrong",
          "Mike Tyson",
          "Boris Johnson",
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    topic: "Music",
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question:
          "Rihanna hit Umbrella was originally written with which other popstar in mind?",
      },
      { id: 2, question: "Which talent show judge managed Westlife?" },
      {
        id: 3,
        question:
          "Which music legend won the Nobel Prize for literature in 2016?",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question:
          "Which single has had the longest uninterrupted run ever on the UK Singles Chart?",
      },
    ],
    answers: [
      {
        correct: "Britney Spears",
        answer: ["Britney Spears", "Eminem", "Taylor Swift", "Mariah Carey"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Louis Walsh",
        answer: [
          "Louis Walsh",
          "Simon Cowell",
          "Gary Barlow",
          "Sharon Osbourne",
        ],
      },
      {
        correct: "Bob Dylan",
        answer: ["Eminem", "Jared Leto", "Bob Dylan", "Anthony Joshua"],
      },
      {
        correct: "Bryan Adams (Everything I Do)",
        answer: [
          "Cheeky Girls (We are the cheeky girls)",
          "Nickelback ('Hero')",
          "Michael Jackson (thriller)",
          "Bryan Adams (Everything I Do)",
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
];

module.exports = quizObject;
